I want to read more of your books, but I
read Run or Die, that's the first one I
read. Like in the early chapters you
talked about, I guess the value you
found in like
endurance and athletic performance. And
I just remember like relating to that so
much where I was just like, man, you
know, like when I when I first got into
running, I had no intentions of going
pro or anything. Like I didn't think I
was capable. But it was so cool when I
could push myself to limits and explore,
you know, explore on mountains and stuff
like that. Like that was just the
coolest thing to me. And so it was
entirely intrinsic motivation.
>> No, that's uh yeah, thanks for that,
man. It's nice to be to inspire guys
like you too to push the things and like
you're putting the
like you moved to to Colorado to be able
to play more